shopnineteen.com 2017-09-05

# Know the Privacy Policy of Shopnineteen

At shopnineteen , we promise to secure your personal information you share with us in good faith.

We take following strict steps when it comes to protecting your privacy on our web sites:

  * For surfing the website we don’t ask for personal information. You can visit us without telling anything about yourself. Having said that, we just like All other websites on internet get access to your IP address (your computer identification address) from which you visit us. We store this data for statistics purposes only. Your personal information is still not recorded here.

  * When you place an order, it’s imperative that we need your personal information like mail ids, phone number, name and address, so that we can facilitate smooth delivery to your door step. We store this information till you don’t get yourself de-registered on our website.

  * For improved service and recommendations for you when you come next time to us, we use a technological tool called "cookies". If you are uncomfortable with us serving you in this manner, you can anytime do changes in your browser setup to notify you when you are sent a cookie, giving you the option to decide whether or not to accept it.

  * shopnineteen will not sell, trade or disclose to third parties any information derived from the registration for, or use of, any online service (including names and addresses) without the consent of the user or customer (except as required by subpoena, search warrant, or other legal process or in the case of imminent physical harm to the user or others).

Don’t Worry!! Your information is very SAFE with us. We will take appropriate steps to protect the information you share with us. We have implemented technology and security features and strict policy guidelines to safeguard the privacy of your personally identifiable information from unauthorized access and improper use or disclosure.

shopnineteen will continue to enhance its security procedures as new technology becomes available.

By accessing this site the user agrees to let shopnineteen use the personal data entered by the user to justify and administrate the business and user relationship, as well as to perform and execute deals and contracts initiated through the website. This particularly concerns the User’s name, address, telephone number , mobile number, email address, sex and date of birth.
